https://bet-grand-national.co.uk/privacy-policy/

The eventHistory of the eventGrand National GuideGrand National JockeysGrand National PromotionsGrand National Ante Post Betting GuideGrand National betting offersGrand National Free BetsGrand National New Customer OffersGrand National Sign Up OffersBetting guideBest BookiesWho To Bet OnGrand National betting onlineGrand National betting tipsEach Way BetsGrand National Betting SitesGrand National StreamingBetting on Grand National 2021Grand National Bet CalculatorRunners and OddsGrand National RunnersGrand National OddsThe BookmakersLadbrokes Grand national offerBetfred Grand national offerBet365 Grand national offerPaddy Power Grand national offerWilliam Hill Grand national offerCoral Grand National offerBetfair Grand national offerSky Bet Grand National offerTote Grand National offer Privacy PolicyCommercial content | New Customers Only | Wagering and Terms and conditions apply | 18+ Privacy StatementThis Privacy Statement is composed of several sections. Please read them all before you continue to use this website.IntroductionThe privacy of all visitors to this website (‘you’) is important. This Privacy Statement is important for you to understand how your personal data is collected, consulted and processed when you use this website.This website is owned by:This Privacy Statement is effective from 25th May 2018.Data We ProcessWe are processing (or may process) various categories of your data, which are grouped into two main types:Your electronic identification dataData of your interaction with our partnered websitesElectronic identification data contains, but is not limited to, the processing of the device type you are accessing our website from, the unique device identifier, your approximate location, the amount of time spent on every web page, your IP address, Operating System installed on your device, browser type and the date and time of access to our website.Secondly, your interaction with our partnered websites includes information such as when you visit sites of our partners (online gambling service providers) and register for a user account. If applicable, we will also look into the scope of your gaming activities on these websites. This type information we process only on aggregated level. In other words, this type of your information is grouped with the same type of data generated by other users. Thus, we cannot find out details exactly about your activities on other websites managed by our partners, but we can find out general statistics about the activities of our users.Personal Data and Reasons for ProcessingBy visiting our website some of your personal data may become the subject of processing. We may gather data for purposes stated below and in accordance to our various legitimate interests explained in this Privacy Statement.We process the IP address of the device you use in order to enable communication between your device and our server, as well as to determine your approximate geolocation which may be further used for service customization (for instance to provide appropriate content for your language of choice and gambling-related content that is legal in your country). We also use this information for analytical purposes (for example to calculate how many visitors from specific countries/regions come to our website).The information about the operating system and browser can also be processed. This is necessary to help with solving technical problems should they appear, ensuring a regular provision of our services to you.We may also process data about your activities taken on our partners’ websites. This type of information is grouped with other similar data to help us create statistics about the use of our services. This is important for the legitimate purpose of calculating our revenue.Your Rights Under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)Since we determine the purposes and means of data processing, we are data controllers over your personal data. We are obliged to protect your data with an utmost caution and in line with data protection laws, namely General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).According to GDPR, you have the right to:Request that we limit our use and processing of your personal data. Withdraw consent to data processing. Request that we erase some or all of your personal data from our storage. Make an objection to how we process or use data. Request access to your personal data. Perform correction of your personal data. Obtain portability of your personal data. Lodge a complaint with the relevant Data Protection Authority.The relevant data protection authority in EU Member States might be determined either by your place of habitual residence, or the place where the alleged infringement emerged.For more information on these rights, or if you want to send us a request concerning your rights, you can contact us atIn Denmark, which is where we are registered, please direct your complaints to the
Danish Data Protection Agency at Datatilsynet, Borgergade 28, 5, DK-1300 Copenhagen K.Lawful Basis for Data ProcessingWe process your personal data for the purpose of pursuing our legitimate interest since it may be necessary in order to keep potential issues with our services to a minimum. Processing personal data can enable us to better our products’ effectiveness and our service to improve your user experience , to develop content on our website through upgrading and advancing our services and products , secure and maintain regular functionality of our website , provide a means of communication and estimate the effectiveness of available advertising .Additionally, mandatory legal obligations may require the processing of your data.Cookie PolicyAny browser visiting our website will receive cookies from us. Cookies are comparatively small files that are stored on your computer that we use to provide third party content, promote our services and products and that help us to generally improve the performance of our website. To find out more about the cookies that we use on our site, please read our Cookie Policy.Protecting Your DataWe do not collect personal data in excessive manner. We are committed to keeping your data up to date and securely stored. The processing will not take longer than necessary for the purpose of it. We apply appropriate technical and organizational measures to ensure the protection of your personal data against :Accidental or unlawful loss,Theft, alteration,Unauthorized disclosure or accessAnd any other kind of unlawful use. Our control of access is structured in multiple levels. Restrictions to access are based on business needs and security requirements. Only staff that are appropriately authorized can access your data if this is a necessity for them to complete assigned work tasks.Sharing Your DataWe reserve the right to share your data with third parties. By ‘third parties’ we refer to individuals, organizations and/or companies that are working in development, marketing, analytics or other fields who help us to provide and further develop our services. For the sake of executing tasks previously agreed upon, the third parties are given the right to process any necessary information. Please note that the right to establish the means and purpose of data processing, including selection of data is exclusively ours. In addition, we may share your data with public authorities and law enforcement agencies where we are legally required to do so and subcontractors and employees of the Better Collective Group, including Better Collective A/S and its’ subsidiaries.Transferring Your Data Outside of the European Economic Area (EEA) Below is an overview of recipients outside of the European Economic Area (EEA) that we may transfer your data to:A recipient based in the US, whereby we aim to transfer your data in the way set out by the Privacy Shield mechanism. More about the EU-US Privacy Shield mechanism is available
here.A recipient in a country that does not have an adequate level of data protection, according to the European Commission. When this is the case, we will conclude Data Protection Agreements that will include Standard Contractual Clauses issued by the European Commission. These Agreements would obligate the data recipient to provide an adequate level of protection and implement appropriate safeguards, as defined by the applicable data protection laws, particularly GDPR.A recipient that is based in a country that does have an adequate level of protection, as approved by the European Commission. A list of countries that provide an adequate level of data protection is available
here We may transfer your personal data outside of the (EEA)as an essential condition for developing or providing our services. In this case, we will take all measures to ensure that your data is transferred in an adequate and secure way and in accordance with the applicable Data Protection Laws.End NotesIt is possible that this Statement will be modified or updated in the future. Updates may contain essential or minor modifications.Essential modifications are announced before application so you are aware of the scope of changes beforehand. Essential modifications may be necessary if we, for instance, launch new services, deploy new technologies and process your data for new purposes. When we make minor modifications to this Privacy Statement, this will not have any influence on your rights or obligations. By continuing to use our website after we publish the updated Privacy Statement with only minor modifications, you accept to be bound by the updated rules.
Bet grand national uses cookies to give you the best user experience. By continuing to use the site you agree to our cookie policy.OkRead more 18+ Play Responsibly
